（悪魔１の荒い息）
（悪魔１のうめき声）
（悪魔２）逃げろ！
Run.
うわあっ！
（悪魔３）こっちだ！ うっ！
This way.
Help me.
助けてくれ！ あああ～！
（デビルマン）はあ…
はあ…
（デビルマンの絶叫）
（車のブレーキ音）
（牧村(まきむら)美樹(みき)）えっ！
（不動(ふどう) 明(あきら)）美樹！
（美樹）はっ！
Miki.
起きてたか
You're awake.
明くん 忍びでも始めたか？
Akira.
Are you a ninja now?
あっ！？ うう…
玄関だと みんな 起こすだろ
（車が去る音）
Using the door would
wake everyone up.
Akira,
you've changed since that guy Ryo came.
（明の荒い息）
あの了って人が来てから
明くん 変わったね
（明の荒い息）
ワイルドなのはいいけど
夜遅いと みんな心配するよ
Going out is fine,
but my parents will worry
if it's this late.
（明）ええい
何かあったら 私に話して
Let me know if you need anything.
（明）ああああ…！
（美樹）家族みたいなもんだろ
We're family.
&lrm;（ターコの鳴き声）
なっ！？ あ…
（美樹）ん？
俺は…
（美樹）うん？
I...
（明）ええい
（美樹）明くん？ ああ…
Akira?
（明のわめき声）
（物を投げる音）
（美樹）はあ…
（シレーヌ）
ああ～ ああっ あああ～！
RESULTS: 1
AKIRA FUDO
（カイム）ううん…
（シレーヌ）ああ～ ああああ～！
ああああ～！
（シレーヌの絶叫）
（明の荒い息）
（飛鳥(あすか) 了）明
Akira.
おい 明
Hey, Akira.
Aren't you a bit too wild, Akira?
（美樹）
ワイルドすぎない？ 明くん
（不動礼次郎(れいじろう)）生きているんだよ
It's alive.
（不動香織(かおり)）きっちり結んでね
Tie it tightly.
（明の荒い息）
（明の絶叫）
（射精の音）
うおああっ！
うっ…
はあ はあ はあ…
あっ？
はっ！？
うっ くっ…
（アナウンサー）
昨日 ２人の警官が
殺された事件の続報です
New details on the murder
of two policemen yesterday.
（アナウンサー）
昨日 ２人の警官が
殺された事件の続報です
Gang members of the Tattoo Crew...
犯人とみられる
イレズミのギャング団は―
SERIAL MURDERS
一連の 多発している
残忍な殺人事件にも―
...are sought for involvement
in the murders,
関係しているとみられ
現在も逃走を続けており…
but are still on the loose. Police are...
（牧村ノエル）
400メートル男女混合リレー？
A mixed 4-by-100-meter relay?
うん 幸田(こうだ)くんのイベントだけど
４継の２走に選ばれた
Yeah. It's Koda's event,
but I've been selected, too.
（牧村太郎(たろう)）
体の発育だけは いいからな
It's just because your body's filled out.
（牧村亜樹子(あきこ)）
どこで覚えたの そんな言い方
Where did you learn to say such things?
Akira's the anchor. Right?
明くんがアンカーなのよ ね？
Well, congratulations.
おお！ おめでとう！
明くんがねえ
Our Akira, huh?
（亜樹子）
明くん 最近 見違えたものね
Akira,
I hardly recognize you lately.
香織も 靴を送り続けた
かいがあったわね
Maybe Kaori sending you shoes
worked some magic.
はい…
-Yes.
-Her last visit was so short...
２年ぶりに帰ってきたのに
トンボ帰りだなんて
after being away for two years.
安心しちゃったのかもね
She must have felt reassured.
甘えたんだろ
You let her spoil you?
はい…
-Yes.
-Again? You really like that, don't you?
また～！？
兄ちゃん 好きだなあ
（陸上部マネージャー）よーい
Get set.
Wow, Miko.
（部員１）すごい ミーコ！
（部員２）記録 出るんじゃない？
-A new record?
-She's faster than Miki!
（部員３）美樹より速いかも！
（部員４）すごい すごい！
Amazing!
（部員５）美樹の記録に並んだよ
-You tied Miki's record.
-How'd you do that?
（部員６）どうしちゃったの？
（ミーコ）美樹は？
（部員４）さあ
-Where's Miki?
-Dunno.
（部員６）
休むって言ってたけど 知らない
She said she wasn't coming today.
（部員４）体調悪いって感じでも
なかったけど
She didn't look ill or anything.
（ミーコ）美樹と並んで走った時
ハッキリと 差をつけてやる
I'll leave Miki way behind
when I run alongside her.
陸上部で一番速いのは
このミキだ！
It's Miki who is the fastest one
in the track club.
KOSHIEN MEMBERS
2: MIKI 3: MIKO 4: AKIRA
2: MIKO
3: MIKI
KEEP OUT
（業者）さあ
２週間前だったと思うけどな
Well, I think it was two weeks ago.
（業者）人がいたって話もあるけど
事件になってないし…
Some say there was a person here,
but there wasn't any incident.
そうですか
どうもありがとうございます
Is that so? Thank you very much.
It's dangerous these days.
最近 物騒だからねえ
お嬢ちゃん このスタジオで
写真 撮るはずだったの… って
You were supposed to model
for a photo shoot at this studio...
（ゼイ）被害は 神奈川地区に
集中している
Kanagawa is affected the most.
これは 偶然ではない
It's no coincidence.
犯人について
まだ手がかりもないというのか？
Don't we have any leads
on the suspect yet?
Find him!
捜せ これは
身内の仕業の可能性もある
This could be the work of one of us.
（シレーヌ）教える必要もない
There's no need to tell him.
私に会えば
アモンは 元の心を取り戻す
If he sees me,
Amon will rediscover his old heart.
（カイム）戻らなかったら？
And if he doesn't?
その時は 私が始末する
Then I'll get rid of him.
I'll suck up just his penis.
男根だけ しゃぶりつくしてな
ふっ
（了）急激に 記録が伸びた理由は
なんですか？
How did he improve his times so much?
（ウェブプロデューサー）
それまでは メンタルが弱い部分も
あったように思いましたが
I think his mental game was
still weak in some ways, but...
（了）急に変わった？
A sudden change?
（ウェブプロデューサー）ええ
人格から見た目もすっかり…
Yes, in his personality.
Even his appearance changed.
（ウェブプロデューサー）こいつ
整形のやりすぎだよな
-This one's had way too much work done.
-She hasn't had any plastic surgery.
（了）彼女は
整形をやっていませんよ
I didn't mean...
（ウェブプロデューサー）
いや 何も！
I-I wasn't thinking that at all.
全く そんなこと考えてません
She's been helping me
since early childhood.
私が幼少のころから
世話を焼いてもらってる―
有能な秘書です
-She's a talented secretary.
-Oh, of course.
もっ もちろんです！
（ウェブプロデューサー）え～！
考えただけなのに 読まれたみたい
What? I only thought it.
It's as if he read my mind.
（ウェブスタッフ）
幸田選手との対談は―
Mr. Koda's interview is scheduled
before the Koshien track event.
陸上甲子園の前に
設定してあります
I'm excited to see you two geniuses
face off, Mr. Asuka.
飛鳥さんとは―
天才対決になりそうで
楽しみです！
（了）
私は 天才じゃありませんよ
I'm not a genius.
This is just...
これは あくまで…
（扉が開く音）
んっ？
Ryo!
（明）了！
俺は どうしたらいい！？
What should I do?!
どうしたらいいんだ！！
（了）ちょっと お待ちください
Excuse me, please.
（２人の驚く声）
（了）明！ 寝室へ行こう
Akira. Let's go to the bedroom.
（明）はあ… はあ…
You used my list without asking.
（了）
俺のリストを勝手に使ったな
お前が１人で行動するとは…
I didn't think you'd act alone.
（明）はあ はあ はあ
殺したくて ぶちのめしたくて
たまらねえ
I want to kill them.
Beat the shit out of them.
でも同時に 悲しくて
大声で わめきたくなる
But I feel sad at the same time.
I feel like crying.
赤ん坊みてえだ
It's like I'm a baby.
（了）人間は メンタルが弱い
Humans have weak minds.
感情で ものを考えると
合理的に答えが出なくなり―
Thinking with emotions
won't yield rational answers,
容量の限界を超えてしまう
and exceeds our capabilities.
そういう時
人間は 忘れるんだ
At times like that,
humans simply forget..
人間には
考えない能力も備わっている
Humans also have the ability to not think.
（明）はあ？
（了）酒 ギャンブル 女
Alcohol, gambling,
women.
そういうものを使って
忘れようとする
They use vices to try and forget.
人間の習慣だ 見習え
It's human habit.
Learn from it.
来週の陸上甲子園で
俺たちの作戦は 第２段階に入る
Phase two of our plan will begin
at Koshien next week.
悪魔が憎いなら―
If you truly hate the demons,
get back to your normal self by then.
それまでに
いつものお前に戻っておけ
（ドアの開閉音）
（部員１）すごかったよ ミーコ
男子も ぼう然
Miko, you were amazing.
The guys were stunned!
（部員２）
イメチェンも かっこいい！
Your new look is cool, too.
ミーコ これ似合うんじゃない？
-Miko, you'd look good in this.
-Thanks.
（ミーコ）ありがと
You're the main runner
in the 4-by-100-meter.
（部員２）混合４継も
ミーコがメインだよ！
You're definitely the fastest.
（部員１）
ナンバーワンに決まってる！
４継は スーパー高校生の
ヨイショイベントだから
The 4-by-100 is just to
butter up the super high-schooler.
（ミーコ）私は 美樹に
100メートルで勝つんだ！
I'm going to beat Miki
in the 100-meter sprint.
（ワム）
ククン 来るか？ こんなとこ
-Will Kukun come to a place like this?
-Nobu said...
（ガビ）ノブの話じゃ…
あんな クソジャンキー
信じられるか
You can't believe that guy.
（ガビ）あ？
ああ…
（客１）はっ！
（客２）ちょっと！
Hey.
（客３）わっ！
（ガビ）おい ククン！
Hey, Kukun.
（ククン似の少年）ああ？
おっと わりい
Oh, my bad.
Wrong guy.
違うか
ったく ククンのヤツ
連絡しねえから
Damn it.
It's because Kukun won't contact us.
うち行ってみよう―
Let's go to his place. We can ask his dad.
あいつのオヤジに聞きゃ
分かるかも
（ククン似の少年）強盗だ！
（ガビ）あ？
Robbery!
そいつ 銃を持ってるぞ！
He has a gun!
That bastard!
あいつ！
（店員）あっ！？ ああ…
（警報）
（客たちの怯える声）
おい 待てよ
Hey!
Wait!
俺は 強盗なんかじゃねえぞ
こら！
Hey, I'm no damn thief!
Help!
（ククン似の少年）助けてー！
（ガビ）ああ？
殺されるー！
He's gonna kill me!
You idiot. I really will kill you!
このガキ
ホントに殺してやろうか！
（警察官１）止まれ！
（ガビ）あっ
Freeze!
Put your hands up and turn around!
（警察官２）手を上げて
こっちを向くんだ！
（警察官２）あっ！ ん…
（ワム）おい やめろ
（警察官２）ああ！
Hey. Stop it.
俺たちは 銃なんか持ってない
We're not carrying guns.
Freeze! One wrong move and I'll shoot!
（警察官２）止まれ！
妙な動きをすると 撃つぞ！
床に伏せて 足を開け 早く！
Face down on the floor
and spread 'em! Now!
（警察官１）
そっちのヤツ！ 手を出せ！
You! Show your hands!
Hie.
ヒエ？
He has a gun!
銃を持ってるぞ！
（警察官１）
ポケットに入ってる物を―
Take whatever's in your pocket out.
Slowly!
ゆっくり つかんで出せ！
（銃声）
（客たちの悲鳴）
早くしろ！ 脅しじゃないぞ
Now! This is your last warning!
（警察官２）いい…
Stop it!
やめなよ！
（ミーコ）あっ！
（ワム）あいつ…
That's...
違うって言ってるよ！
話くらい聞いたら？
He's saying they're not thieves.
Hear them out!
ほら あんたも手出して
And, you, take your hands out.
（警察官１）録音機か…
A recorder.
もちろん 話は 聞かせてもらう
We've got some questions to ask.
取調室で？
In an interrogation room?
今 連れてかれたら―
Rumors will spread if you
take them into custody now.
ここにいるみんなは
きっと 言いふらしちゃうよ
（客）あれ 牧村美樹じゃない？
Isn't that Miki Makimura?
（店員）ちょっと待って 君！
-You! Wait a second!
-Hey, kid!
（ガビ）ちょー ガキー！
何だよ！
あっちは 撃たねえのかよ！
Hey, aren't you gonna shoot him?
ん… 通報は
確認をしっかり お願いしますよ
Make sure you call this in right.
You guys can go.
お前たちは もういい！
What the hell? No apology?
ざけんなよ！
こっちには謝んねえのか！
おわびに Ｔシャツぐらいくれても
いんじゃねえか？
Can't you at least give us free T-shirts?
もういいよ
悪いのは 分かってると思う
Let it go.
I think they know they screwed up.
はあ…
（部員１）すごいよ 美樹
-That was amazing!
-You were so cool!
かっこよかったー
（美樹）いたんだ
-You were watching?
-Those cops were jerks.
警官 態度悪いよねー
見た目だけで
They judge by looks.
（部員２）
雰囲気で先導される人 多いよね
So many people get riled up in the moment.
（美樹）みんな 怖いから
They just get scared.
Hey.
（ワム）おい
（美樹）あ…
助かった 礼を言っとく
牧村美樹
You saved us. Thank you, Miki Makimura.
いや 間違ってるの
よくないから
Not at all.
I had to do what was right.
男って どいつも
言葉足りなさすぎで―
Men don't explain themselves well enough.
１人で 黙って
死んじゃったり―
They'll shut up and die alone,
突然 わめいたり…
（ワム）あ？
Or yell out of nowhere.
おっ ごめん こっちの話だ
Oops, sorry. Forget what I said.
（婆さん１）兄さん
寄ってきなよ いい子いるよ
Stop in for a visit, young man.
We have nice girls.
（婆さん２）
ほらほら 決めちゃいなよ
Come on, come on. Just for a bit.
さあ どうぞ どうぞ
Make yourself at home.
うふふ
たんまりさん ご案内だよ
Show him in.
（女の子１）ありがとー
いっぱい サービスするね
I've got something special for you.
On the house.
（明）うう… うう… うう…
（女の子２）いい男じゃん
He's handsome.
（婆さん１）やめときな
ありゃ 人殺してるよ
Don't.
He's killed people.
（女の子２）あ…
（シレーヌ）お兄さん
Hey, there.
ねえ 私のこと 覚えてない？
Do you remember me?
おいで
Come here.
思い出させてあげる
I'll make you remember.
Silene.
シレーヌ
You are beautiful.
君は美しい
Beautiful Silene
あなた 名前は？
What's your name?
明
Akira.
I see. Do you like that name?
そう その名前好き？
ああ 今は別の名前がある
Yeah.
I've got another one, too.
なあに それ
Tell me.
言いたくない
I don't want to.
隠しても分かるわよ
You can't hide it from me.
（明）んんっ
PRICES
（明の荒い息）
（明の荒い声）
（明）ああ…
教えて あなたの本当の名前
Tell me your real name.
ああっ！
たけだけしくて 荒々しい
お前の真実
The fierce and rough truth of you.
（明の荒い声）
（シレーヌ）なあ 言え
Say it.
言えよ！
Say it!
（明の荒い声）
（シレーヌ）名前を言え！
Say your name!
うわああああっ！
（シレーヌ）目を覚ませ アモン！
私だ シレーヌだ！
Wake up, Amon.
It's me, Silene!
I was lonely, Amon.
（明）ぐああ… うう…
（シレーヌ）寂しかったよ アモン
I waited so long
for you to come to the human realm.
お前が人間の世界に来るのを
どれほど待ったことか！
（カイム）んんん…
ぬうう…
ふー…
（明）いいところに来た！
You came at a good time.
I didn't real want to screw a woman.
I'm dying to slam a demon.
女を抱く以上に 俺は―
悪魔をぶちのめしたくて
しかたなかったんだ！！
おお！ その姿は
やはりアモン！
That form! You are Amon!
No. My name is...
（デビルマン）
違う！ 俺の名は―
Devilman!
デビルマンだ！！
うああ！
（デビルマン）んっ
ううっ ぬう！
（ドラム缶が転がる音）
（デビルマン）うっ
うおおおお！
えい！
Beautiful moon. If you don't wish
to be stained with unsightly blood,
（シレーヌ）美しい月よ！
醜い血で染まりたくないならば―
ズタズタに引き裂かれる悪魔を
見ぬがよい！
don't look at the demon
about to be ripped to shreds.
（デビルマン）ううっ
がっ ぐああ…
（シレーヌ）目覚めよ アモン！
そして その腕で私を抱け！
Wake up, Amon!
Embrace me. Make love to me.
強く！ 激しく！
Strong...and hard!
抱け？
Make love?
I wanted to hug you.
（香織）抱いてあげたかった
（デビルマン）うう…
うう～！！
勝手なことを言うな！
No more selfish talk.
俺を抱いてくれた人たちを！
You kill the people who embraced me.
（シレーヌ）ふっ
You!
（デビルマン）お前らは！！
があ！
（シレーヌのうめき声）
-How dare you?
-If you want to get fucked that badly...
よくも…
（デビルマン）
そんなに抱かれたいなら！
（シレーヌのもだえる声）
I'll fuck you!
（デビルマン）抱いてやる！
（シレーヌ）うあああ！
Damn you!
クソめ！ んっ！
（デビルマン）があ！
（シレーヌ）うあああ！
（カイム）ぬああああ！
シレーヌ！
Silene!
（シレーヌ）おのれ おのれ…
許さんぞ デビルマン
You bastard.
I'll never forgive you, Devilman!
人間の分際で アモンを奪い―
How dare a mere human take my Amon away,
このシレーヌにまで
屈辱を与えるとは！
and humiliate even me, Silene?
（カイム）シレーヌ
Silene.
Use my body.
俺の体を使え！ 合体だ！
Merge with me.
合体？ 何を言う カイム！
Merge? What are you talking about, Kaim?
この傷が分からないのか？
Do you not see my wounds?
私は もう死ぬ
I'll be dead soon.
それを承知で言っている
I'm aware of that.
You'll die, too,
even if we merge and kill Devilman.
（シレーヌ）合体して
デビルマンを倒しても―
お前は 死ぬのだ！
俺も生きのびるつもりはない
I don't intend to survive.
（シレーヌ）うう…
（カイム）君に デビルマンを倒す
勝利の感激を味わわせたいだけだ
I just want you to feel the rush
of a triumph over this Devilman.
俺の命と能力を君にやろう
I will give you my life and power.
（シレーヌ）ああ… なぜ？
Why?
（カイム）
シレーヌ 血まみれでも―
Silene.
Even covered in blood...
you are the vision of beauty.
君は 美しい
カイム！
Kaim!
（シレーヌ）
月よ！ シレーヌの執念が―
Hear me, moon!
Bear witness as the vengeance of Silene
and the life of Kaim end Devilman!
カイムの命が
デビルマンを殺すところを見よ！
Shit!
やばい！
（デビルマン）うあああ！
（デビルマン）動けない…
I can't move.
戻ってくる 逃げろ！ 逃げろ！
She's coming.
Run. Run away.
（デビルマン）ぐえ！
（デビルマン）抜けていく…
I'm losing it.
（明）力が…
My power.
シレーヌ…
Silene.
なぜ とどめを刺しに来ない…？
Why aren't you coming to finish me?
お前は 勝ったんだぞ…
You've won.
Akira? Get a hold of yourself.
（了）明
しっかりしろ 明！
Akira.
（明）ああ…
（了）はあ
（明）俺は… 生きてるのか？
Am I alive?
（了）辛うじてな
Barely.
飲め
Drink this.
ああ…
了 お前
どうして ここに？
Ryo.
Why are you here?
虫の知らせってやつかな
I had a gut feeling.
悪魔の力を持っても
その傷とは
Even with demon powers,
you suffered that wound.
はっ！
ああ…
そうだ シレーヌ！
That's right. Silene.
俺は シレーヌという悪魔と
戦っていた
I was fighting a demon named Silene.
あいつは なぜ俺に
とどめを刺さなかった？
Why didn't she finish me off?
簡単に殺せたはずなのに…
She could have killed me easily.
そういうことか
（明）あ？
I see.
悪魔なら 向こうにいる
見るといい
The demon is over there.
Take a look.
（明）うっ うう…
（明）あっ！？
She's dead.
死んでる
立ち往生ってやつだな
She died on her feet.
おそらく お前にとどめを刺す前に
こと切れた
Probably just before
she was able to finish you.
あ…
（了）自分の勝利を
確信していたんだろう
She looks confident of her victory.
満足しきった顔をしている
The look of pure satisfaction.
Ryo.
（明）了
（了）ん？
（明）
悪魔にも 愛があるのか？
Do demons know how to love?
（了）まさか
It's unlikely.
悪魔は ある意味 純粋な生物だ
Demons are pure creatures in a way.
破壊衝動 捕食活動が
彼らの全てだ
The hunt and their destructive urge
are everything to them.
（明）そうか…
I see.
To me...
俺には 愛に見えた
it was love.
&lrm;
Subtitles by
Kristine Kenmochi